export const quizData = [
    {
            "question": "Identify the most reasonable unit to measure the height of a coffee cup?",
            "options": [
                "Centimeters",
                "Meters",
                "Kilometers",
                "Nanometers"
            ],
            "answer": 1
    },
    {
            "question": "Which is closer to the volume of a paint bucket?",
            "options": [
                "4 Liters",
                "4 Millimeters",
                "4 Gallon",
                "0.4 Millimeters"
            ],
            "answer": 1
    },
    {
            "question": "Kathiva has a baby pool in her backyard. Yesterday, the pool had 425 liters of water in it. This afternoon, Kathiva used a hose to add 23 more liters of water How many liters of water are in the baby pool now?",
            "options": [
                "425 liters",
                "402 liters",
                "23 liters",
                "448 liters"
            ],
            "answer": 4
    },
    {
            "question": "Kirsten has 9 syrup containers from a local cafe. There are 6 milliliters of syrup per container. \n How many milliliters of syrup does Kirsten have?",
            "options": [
                "9 mL",
                "15 mL",
                "6 mL",
                "54 mL"
            ],
            "answer": 4
    },
    {
            "question": "Identify the most reasonable unit to measure the volume of a pond?",
            "options": [
                "Millimeters",
                "Litres"
            ],
            "answer": 2
    },
    {
            "question": "Ahmed made a fruit smoothie in his blender 625 mL, shown below. He gave 320 milliliters of the smoothie to his brother?",
            "options": [
                "300",
                "305",
                "330",
                "310"
            ],
            "answer": 2
    },
    {
            "question": "Ayumi puts 3 packets of ketchup on her tater tots. The volume of each packet of ketchup 8 mL?",
            "options": [
                "8",
                "20",
                "24",
                "16"
            ],
            "answer": 2
    },
    {
            "question": "Which is the closest to the mass of a baby chick?",
            "options": [
                "25 grams",
                "25 kilograms"
            ],
            "answer": 1
    },
    {
            "question": "Jessica is making desserts. One box of cookies weighs 263 grams. The brownies weigh 572 grams.How much do both of the desserts weigh combined?",
            "options": [
                "572 grams",
                "263 grams",
                "835 grams",
                "309 grams"
            ],
            "answer": 3
    },
];




// [
//     {
//         question: "Which language runs in a web browser?",
//         options:[ "Java", "C", "Python", "JavaScript"],
//         answer: 4
//     },
//     {
//         question: "What does CSS stand for?",
//         options:["Central Style Sheets", "Cascading Style Sheets", "Cascading Simple Sheets", "Cars SUVs Sailboats"],
//         answer: 2
//     },
//     {
//         question: "What does HTML stand for?",
//         options: ["Hypertext Markup Language", "Hypertext Markdown Language", "Hyperloop Machine Language", "Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis"],
//         answer: 1
//     },
//     {
//         question: "What year was JavaScript launched?",
//         options: ["1996", "1995", "1994", "none of the above"],
//         answer: 2
//     },
// ];









